Help them! Hurry!
A crash! Is anyone hurt? There's someone inside!
Call for help! Call for help!
Even now, I still don't know
how Fu Yan planned all of this.
The Fu Yan back then
seemed like a completely different person.
After causing such a huge disaster,
how did he clean it up?
No one saw him.
In the end, it was handled
as the client's drunk driving.
Do you know
why he did this?
He wanted to protect me.
Everything you've been enjoying
hasn't come without a price.
He is someone who shouldn't even exist.
In each reincarnation,
he inevitably has to lose something,
eventually turning into a complete stranger.
Then what can I do to stop him?
You can't.
It's time to let go.
His repeated disappearances
prove that he wants to leave, too.
You're back.
You must be tired.
I'm alright.
Wait for me.
I'm almost done writing.
Why are the lights off?
It's quite comfortable like this.
I'll go make you some Sweet fermented rice with egg.
Not right now.
How did the writing go today?
I had a new idea today.
The Final Showdown.
Have the hero and the villain die together.
Why is that?
Because he's already lost everything.
He doesn't even have any enemies left.
Death, for him,
is actually a release.
Have you really thought this through?
Maybe this is the best ending.
I'll cook.
I'll do it.
What?
Let me do it today.
Okay.
Then what should I do?
Go write something else.
What should I
write?
Write whatever you want.
Okay.
If he just takes this,
he'll disappear.
Didn't we say we'd wait a full seven years
to drink it when the seven-year itch hits?
I want to drink it today.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
This stuff tastes awful.
Did something happen?
Yeah.
Come on.
Hold out your hands. Come on.
What is this?
I saw a kid today.
I thought it was really funny.
This is way too cute.
Right?
I haven't even told you yet.
How did you know I was...
Come on, stand up.
Get in. Go.
You won't remember at all.
You won't remember being in a car crash.
Or that you're already dead.
I...
Today I...
I saw a kid playing today.
I thought it was really funny.
I thought it was so funny.
Drink.
I saw a kid playing today.
I thought it was so funny. You drink first.
Drink up first. I thought it was so funny.
I saw a kid playing today.
I thought it was so funny.
Drink. Today I...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I remember now. I really am dead.
Fu Yan.
Don't disappear.
You did the right thing.
This is the best ending.